# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Thompson Manda

Web Developer & Graphics Designer

+90 535 959 8057

in

(7)

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a highly skilled professional, and self-motivated individual with over 3 years' experience working in diverse environments. My interests lie within Engineering, innovation and Technology. My expertise includes a good understanding of user interface design and experience as well as programming and development of web and mobile applications.

I further have extensive knowledge of the widely used computer software packages i.e., Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Adobe XD, Figma among others. I have knowlegde of the web technologies and programming languages including semanatic HTML 5, CSS, Javascript and Python. I possess strong supervision and organizational skills and a good understanding of being a team player especially through changes but can work autonomously when required. I pride myself on being personable, approachable and having the ability to quickly learn new things.

#### **EDUCATION**

BSC. ELECTRIC-ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING

10/2017 - 08/2021

ABANT IZZET BAYSAL UNIVERSITY ~ Bolu, Turkey.

TURKISH LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

ABANT IZZET BAYSAL UNIVERSITY

~ Bolu, Turkey.

09/2016 - 07/2017

#### **SKILLS**

Communication

Computer Programming

Problem Solving

Design

Public Speaking

Engineering

## **CODING & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

Semantic HTML 5

• Python

Modern CSS

Python - Django

JavaScript

Dart & Flutter (Beginner)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FREELANCE WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

05/2018 - PRESENT

INTER-WEBB CORP. / KRYPIA & AFRICAN ARTS FOR SPACES

Working for 3 companies offering freelance services in graphic designs, web design & development of user interfaces (UI) and user experiences (UX). Creating products on the web with modern designs and trends using Content management systems i.e. (Wordpress) as well as pure code to bring to life solutions.

#### GRAPHICS DESIGNER & CONTENT CREATOR

03/2017 - 11/2020

INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS ASSOCIATION (BAIBU UNIVERSITY)

Designing and creating content for the students association board to be posted on social media platforms. Leveraging software packages like Adobe Illustrator to create logos, adverts and social media posts.

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

# WEBB-GRAPHICS - [Graphic Design & Branding]

A part-time freelance graphic design business to help develop my skills in the aspect of graphic design and user expericence. See portfolio, visit: https://webbgraphics.inter-webb.com/
05/2018 - Present

#### • INTERWEBB BUSINESS CORPORATION [IWBC]

A network hub for young entreprenuers both in Zambia and Turkey who have the zeal to develop themselves and make a better standard of living using current tecnonolgies and creativity.

visit: https://inter-webb.com/

## **OTHER ACHIEVEMENTS & CERTIFICATES**

## ICT TEAM LEADER/CAPTAIN

ST JOHN'S SECONDARY SCHOOL

Information Communications Technology club president and school prefect. Encouraging the safe uses of technology. ~Mongu, Zambia.

## WORLD YOUTH FORUM ATTENDEE

WYF - WORLD YOUTH FORUM, EGYPT

A world youth conference for the youth to discuss matters of creating a better world that everyone dreams of with peace and prosperity.

~Sharm El Sheik, Egypt.

# **LANGUAGES**

- English (Fluent)
- Turkish (Proficient Level C1)
- Zambian local Languages
  - ChiBemba ChiNyanja Silozi

# PROFESSIONAL, ACADEMIC AND CHARACTER REFEREES UPON REQUEST

# **DECLARATION**

I the undersigned, do hereby certify and declare that to the best of my knowledge and belief, the above describes myself, my true qualifications, experience, capability and competency.